It was probably not in my taste.
- (Laura) eww.
- (Harry) eww.
What points do you give from 0-5?
- I give 2. - ooh!
I give...
- Oh no, she vomits here.
- ... a light zero.
- Zero, zero, zero ... - zero, superhero!
- Harry, did you notice what just happened here?
- No.
- She vomits type.
Laura, was it good?
- Ah ... no!
- I give this a 3rd.
- I also give a 3rd.
Gimme, Gimme, Gimme Some Time to Think I'm in the Bathroom, Looking at Me
- Are you ashamed of me a little?
- (Harry) ... is all in need.
Gimme, Gimme, Gimme Some Time to Think I'm in the Bathroom, Looking at Me
"Old -fashioned Lakrids"
- But now we drive, I think.
- Here we go!
Okay then.
Oh, sweet chalk.
Or, well ... it was probably a little salty anyway.
That tasted good.
I'll take one more.
How can you dislike licorice so much?
Does all the kids do that?
No.
- No.
Only you are so stupid.
(Alma) eww.
No, I can't do this.
- (Laura) No, Blä.
- You don't like it either?
"No, blow."
But then ... is there a lot of licorice in Iceland?
- Do you need help up, right?
- Yes thank you.
Ouch.
Harry ...
God, you are too snappy.
(Alma Harry) I am a poor peasant boy, but I still live
"Lakkrís Rjómasúkkulaði Með Lakkrísbitum"
(The others laugh)
It looks like a very common piece of chocolate stuck with small tubers on the underside.
- It feels like we've eaten the same thing now and time again.
- Yes.
- Chocolate with licorice in. - Yes.
It is getting a little tedious.
- This one had sweet chalk in anyway.
- huh?
I think it tastes salty.
I seem to have a little trouble with that with sweet and salty, but it's licorice in.
- mm.
Small type sticky squares.
- Yes.
I think this tastes old cheek egg chocolate with burnt car tires in.
I give this chocolate 1 point.
I give this chocolate ... noooool!
Noooool!
Zero.